<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fields xmlns:xfdf="http://ns.adobe.com/xfdf-transition/"
><Dateofbirth xfdf:original="Date of birth"
>28.11.1989</Dateofbirth
><Name
>Falcon</Name
><Sex
>M</Sex
><Height
>1,74 m</Height
><Weight
>73 kg</Weight
><Bloodtype xfdf:original="Blood type"
>B-</Bloodtype
><Rank
>Junior Data Analyst</Rank
><Securitylevel xfdf:original="Security level"
>C</Securitylevel
><Signature
>Falcon</Signature
><Date
>21-02-2024</Date
><Employeecode xfdf:original="Employee code"
>IT23-20</Employeecode
><Department
>Medical Data Department</Department
><Background
>Custom character
The person that would become Falcon always had a love for birds and exploration and would often go out birdwatching. He would often help when he could in minor things, first just leaving out birdfeed. but later this moved on to helping take care of the rare injured birds he would stumble across.
During this time he managed to get a pretty good relationship with a Falcon that he would often see. That started after he took care of his broken wing.
One day During a trip back from seeing his bird friend he stumbled onto a cave. He had walked around that area many times before and never seen it so he got curious. After a quick trip home to gather supplies for exploration, he ventured into the cave. He didn't expect too find much, but he had too se.
He was stunned when he found a strange liquid at the lowest parts of the tunnel. He didn't recognise it but assumed it to be some kind of industrial waste. when he went too leave the cave he slipped and fell into the liquid. He realised that the liquid wasn't accidic at least, and crawled out as fast as possible. He crawled out of the cave, cleaned himself up and made his way home, wanting to take a shower to get rid of what still remained on him. 
During the coming days he found that he changed somewhat. His eyesight improved, he seemed too understand the birds when he visited them and he got lighter. It wasn't long until he found ways to change into a different form that was slightly smaller och lighter but gave the gift of flight thanks to a pair of wings he grew out of his back. He would find ways to use his new abilities to help out both human and animal alike and would eventually take on the alias Falcon</Background
><Strengths
>The strange liquid made him "attune" to the last animal species he touched.(think tmnt but stranger)
Having this "attunement" with a bird of prey, the falcon. gives him many advantages related to said bird. This includes improved eyesight, allowing him to se whats happening from a lot farther away. 
Another power is the power of flight, achieved through a strange new abiltiy to shapeshift. This aerial advantage is great as few people look up most of the time. He also gained the ability too communicate with birds, which was useful with certain bird species.
</Strengths
><Weaknesses
>The biggest weakness Falcon has is that while in flight mode. his bones become hollow. This makes it easier too stay up in the air but also makes him weaker to blunt force. Being lighter also means that he won't win a battle with pure strength. Forcing him to rely on speed and agility to fight when he needs to. </Weaknesses
></fields>