<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fields xmlns:xfdf="http://ns.adobe.com/xfdf-transition/"
><Dateofbirth xfdf:original="Date of birth"
>01.01.1993</Dateofbirth
><Name
>Feathers McGraw</Name
><Sex
>M</Sex
><Height
>90cm</Height
><Weight
>5.4kg</Weight
><Bloodtype xfdf:original="Blood type"
>B-</Bloodtype
><Rank
>Junior Data Analyst</Rank
><Securitylevel xfdf:original="Security level"
>C</Securitylevel
><Signature
>F. McGraw</Signature
><Date
>21.08.2025</Date
><Employeecode xfdf:original="Employee code"
>IT25 - 26</Employeecode
><Department
>Medical Data Department</Department
><Background
>Feathers McGraw is a slick, silent penguin who doesn’t say a word, but his actions speak for him. He first showed up in The Wrong Trousers, where he quickly became a notorious villain. Feathers isn’t just any penguin; he’s a smooth operator with a knack for stealing and getting away with it, all while staying out of sight. He’s got a sharp mind, and he’s always one step ahead of the people trying to stop him.</Background
><Strengths
>Stealth: Feathers is great at sneaking around unnoticed. He can blend in, use disguises, and stay hidden until it’s time to strike.  Brains: He’s smart, always thinking of clever ways to pull off a crime or get out of a tight spot. He doesn’t rely on force, just his wits.  Silent but Deadly: Even though he never speaks, Feathers is great at communicating through his actions and expressions. He makes people nervous without saying a word.  Quick on His Feet: Whether it’s stealing something or escaping, he’s adaptable and able to come up with a plan on the fly.  Feathers McGraw is the kind of villain who doesn’t need to shout to be feared. He’s quiet, clever, and always in control.</Strengths
><Weaknesses
>Feathers McGraw has a few weaknesses that even his cleverness can’t hide. He’s often overconfident, believing he’s always the smartest one in the room, which can lead to careless mistakes. His focus on winning can make him miss important details. He also tends to underestimate Gromit, not realizing how sharp the dog actually is. While Feathers is a mastermind, he’s not physically strong, so if he gets caught off guard, he can struggle to break free. Finally, his impatience can get the best of him. When things don’t go as planned, he tends to act too quickly, making decisions that end up backfiring.</Weaknesses
></fields>