<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fields xmlns:xfdf="http://ns.adobe.com/xfdf-transition/"
><Dateofbirth xfdf:original="Date of birth"
>November 10, 1964</Dateofbirth
><Name
>Sportacus</Name
><Sex
>M</Sex
><Height
>175cm</Height
><Weight
>86kg</Weight
><Bloodtype xfdf:original="Blood type"
>O+</Bloodtype
><Rank
>Junior Data Analyst</Rank
><Securitylevel xfdf:original="Security level"
>C</Securitylevel
><Signature
>Sportacus</Signature
><Date
>21.08.25</Date
><Employeecode xfdf:original="Employee code"
>IT25-09</Employeecode
><Department
>Medical Data Department</Department
><Background
>Sportacus 10 was a boy in LazyTown, named Alex. His adversary was another boy named Robbie which teased him. Sportacus 9 came along and convinced the kids to exercise and gave Alex the Sportacus 10 costume. Robbie later became Robbie Rotten and remained the adversary of Sportacus 10. 

Sportacus name in English is a portmanteau of the ancient figure Spartacus and the word sport, which represents his athleticism. Sportacus humbly describes himself as a "slightly above-average hero", though his friends have a higher opinion of him, calling him a "superhero". 

Sportacus encourages the children of LazyTown to eat fruits and vegetables (which he calls "sports candy") and play outside instead of sitting around indoors and eating unhealthy food. He wants to make sure LazyTown is happy, and knows that its residents have to be healthy and fit if they want to be happy. He is opposed by the sinister (yet equally energetic) Robbie Rotten, who seeks to return LazyTown to its former state: a lazy town. Sportacus is so engaged in his life of physical activity that he does parkour just to get from place to place—even doing acrobatic flips just to get from one side of his kitchen table to the other—and the children have to instruct him on how to relax.




</Background
><Strengths
>Sportacus possesses superhuman strength, agility, and stamina, along with a unique ability to enhance his powers with "sports candy" (fruits and vegetables). He is also a skilled pilot, marksman, and possesses a crystal that can detect danger. </Strengths
><Weaknesses
>Sportacus's primary weakness in LazyTown is his susceptibility to sugar. When he consumes sugary foods, especially Robbie Rotten's "sugar apple," he experiences a "sugar meltdown," rendering him weak and potentially unconscious.</Weaknesses
></fields>