<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fields xmlns:xfdf="http://ns.adobe.com/xfdf-transition/"
><Dateofbirth xfdf:original="Date of birth"
>01.01.1600</Dateofbirth
><Name
>The Void</Name
><Sex
>M</Sex
><Height
>2</Height
><Weight
>200</Weight
><Bloodtype xfdf:original="Blood type"
>A</Bloodtype
><Rank
>Junior Data Analyst</Rank
><Securitylevel xfdf:original="Security level"
>C</Securitylevel
><Signature
>The Void</Signature
><Date
>21.8.2025</Date
><Employeecode xfdf:original="Employee code"
>IT25-27</Employeecode
><Department
>Medical Data Department</Department
><Background
>Though the exact origin of the Void is unknown, his first activities were seemingly traced all the way back to circa 1600 BCE, when Moses pleaded for every Hebrew doorpost to be marked with lamb's blood in order to protect the Jewish firstborn from the final plague God was going to bring on Pharaoh Ramses and on Egypt: the Angel of Death, believed to be the Void himself (though other beings have been told to be that entity). </Background
><Strengths
>Matter Manipulation: The Void possesses similar matter and energy manipulation abilities as the Sentry. Having used it to entrap the Avengers within an inescapable shroud of black matter he had conjured up, material easily able to hold the likes of Thor and Giant-Man with ease. At its most focused i.e. through his tendrils, the Void can cause total atomic cancellation within a target, as he did when he disintegrated the immortal Loki.

Regeneration: The Void can heal himself from virtually all injuries.

Resurrection: The Void appears to be able to resurrect himself and to bring the dead back to life under extreme emotional distress.</Strengths
><Weaknesses
>Magic: The Void can be sealed with powerful magic, as was done by Doctor Strange.

Chi: The Void was proven to be vulnerable to spiritual energy attacks like Chi.

Domination of darkness: The Void being technically a dark entity, any deity with control over other beings of darkness can bend his will.</Weaknesses
></fields>