<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fields xmlns:xfdf="http://ns.adobe.com/xfdf-transition/"
><Dateofbirth xfdf:original="Date of birth"
>22.02.2002</Dateofbirth
><Name
>Beast Boy</Name
><Sex
>M</Sex
><Height
>1.72</Height
><Weight
>68</Weight
><Bloodtype xfdf:original="Blood type"
>O-</Bloodtype
><Rank
>Junior Data Analyst</Rank
><Securitylevel xfdf:original="Security level"
>C</Securitylevel
><Signature
>Beast Boy</Signature
><Date
>21.08.2025</Date
><Employeecode xfdf:original="Employee code"
>IT25-04</Employeecode
><Department
>Medical Data Department</Department
><Background
>As a young child, Garfield Logan lived with his scientist parents in Africa, who were developing "reverse evolution" to bring back extinct creatures. He received a certain amount of abuse from his parents, consequently becoming increasingly reclusive. Garfield contracted a rare illness called Sakutia, which is lethal to every species except the West African green monkey. To save his life, his father used an untested science experiment to change him into a West African green monkey for 24 hours so that the virus could die out. The serum had the unintended effect of permanently turning his skin, eyes, and hair green and granting him the ability to transform into any animal of his choice, which also shared his pigmentation.[8] His parents later died in a boating accident; to this day, Garfield believes he could have prevented their deaths.</Background
><Strengths
>Shapeshifting:
Beast Boy can transform into any animal, granting him access to a vast array of physical abilities like flight, strength, speed, and more, depending on the chosen form.
Versatility:
His shapeshifting allows him to adapt to various situations, making him a valuable asset in combat, reconnaissance, and support roles.
Adaptability:
Over time, Beast Boy has shown the ability to learn and adapt to new animal forms, even those from other planets or realms.</Strengths
><Weaknesses
>Loss of Control:
In some storylines, Beast Boy has struggled to maintain control over his transformations, particularly after traumatic events. 
Dependence on Animal Knowledge:
His effectiveness relies on his knowledge of animal forms and their abilities. If he encounters an unfamiliar creature, he may be less effective. 
Exertion:
Transforming and maintaining animal forms can be physically taxing, and excessive transformations can lead to exhaustion or even temporary loss of his powers. </Weaknesses
></fields>